{
  "level": 4,
  "unit": 4,
  "vocabulary": [
    {
      "week": "12",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "A _____________ is an account given in a particular way.",
          "answer": "version"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "_____________ means “in the end” or “finally.”",
          "answer": "eventually"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "To _____________ means “to reach agreement by having each side give up some of its demands.”",
          "answer": "compromise"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "A _____________ is a sense of obligation toward something.",
          "answer": "commitment"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "_____________ are formal changes made according to official procedures.",
          "answer": "amendments"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "A _____________ is a government that is run by the people who live under it.",
          "answer": "democracy"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "_____________ means “laws that are made or passed.”",
          "answer": "legislation"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "A _____________ is a special right or benefit held by a certain group of people.",
          "answer": "privilege"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "34",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "A _____________ is a period of ten years.",
          "answer": "decade"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "When something is _____________, it is shining or glowing.",
          "answer": "gleaming"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "_____________ means to have looked at or explored in order to find out and bring back more information.",
          "answer": "scouted"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "To have _____________ is to have turned and twisted the body.",
          "answer": "squirmed"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "_____________ is puttering or keeping busy in an aimless way.",
          "answer": "tinkering"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "_____________ is the use of science for practical purposes, especially in engineering and industry.",
          "answer": "technology"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "_____________ is the work that uses scientific knowledge for practical things such as building bridges and dams.",
          "answer": "engineering"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "_____________ is the act of giving instructions, ordering, or commanding.",
          "answer": "directing"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "5",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "When something is a _____________, it is a great victory or success.",
          "answer": "triumph"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "A _____________ object stays in one place in the air.",
          "answer": "hovering"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "To _____________ something is to work hard to achieve a goal.",
          "answer": "attain"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "_____________ means “hanging or swinging loosely.\"",
          "answer": "dangling"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "When you repeat words, you are using _____________.",
          "answer": "repetition"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "A _____________ in a poem can contain any number of lines.",
          "answer": "stanza"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "If I say the tree is scrawny, the _____________ is different from saying the tree is thin.",
          "answer": "connotation"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The _____________ of joyful is “full of joy.”",
          "answer": "denotation"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
